[
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "1",
            "sentence": "SOCCER - JAPAN GET LUCKY WIN , CHINA IN SURPRISE DEFEAT .",
            "label": {
                "JAPAN": "LOC",
                "CHINA": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: SOCCER - JAPAN GET LUCKY WIN , CHINA IN SURPRISE DEFEAT .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "2",
            "sentence": "Nadim Ladki",
            "label": {
                "Nadim Ladki": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Nadim Ladki\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "3",
            "sentence": "AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "AL-AIN": "LOC",
                "United Arab Emirates": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "7",
            "sentence": "Oleg Shatskiku made sure of the win in injury time , hitting an unstoppable left foot shot from just outside the area .",
            "label": {
                "Oleg Shatskiku": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Oleg Shatskiku made sure of the win in injury time , hitting an unstoppable left foot shot from just outside the area .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "8",
            "sentence": "The former Soviet republic was playing in an Asian Cup finals tie for the first time .",
            "label": {
                "Soviet": "MISC",
                "Asian Cup": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: The former Soviet republic was playing in an Asian Cup finals tie for the first time .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "9",
            "sentence": "Despite winning the Asian Games title two years ago , Uzbekistan are in the finals as outsiders .",
            "label": {
                "Asian Games": "MISC",
                "Uzbekistan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Despite winning the Asian Games title two years ago , Uzbekistan are in the finals as outsiders .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "12",
            "sentence": "It was the second costly blunder by Syria in four minutes .",
            "label": {
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: It was the second costly blunder by Syria in four minutes .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "14",
            "sentence": "Nader Jokhadar had given Syria the lead with a well-struck header in the seventh minute .",
            "label": {
                "Nader Jokhadar": "PER",
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Nader Jokhadar had given Syria the lead with a well-struck header in the seventh minute .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "16",
            "sentence": "Bitar pulled off fine saves whenever they did .",
            "label": {
                "Bitar": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Bitar pulled off fine saves whenever they did .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "17",
            "sentence": "Japan coach Shu Kamo said : ' ' The Syrian own goal proved lucky for us .",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC",
                "Shu Kamo": "PER",
                "Syrian": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Japan coach Shu Kamo said : ' ' The Syrian own goal proved lucky for us .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "18",
            "sentence": "The Syrians scored early and then played defensively and adopted long balls which made it hard for us . '",
            "label": {
                "Syrians": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: The Syrians scored early and then played defensively and adopted long balls which made it hard for us . '\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "19",
            "sentence": "'",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: '\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "20",
            "sentence": "Japan , co-hosts of the World Cup in 2002 and ranked 20th in the world by FIFA , are favourites to regain their title here .",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC",
                "World Cup": "MISC",
                "FIFA": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Japan , co-hosts of the World Cup in 2002 and ranked 20th in the world by FIFA , are favourites to regain their title here .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "21",
            "sentence": "Hosts UAE play Kuwait and South Korea take on Indonesia on Saturday in Group A matches .",
            "label": {
                "UAE": "LOC",
                "Kuwait": "LOC",
                "South Korea": "LOC",
                "Indonesia": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Hosts UAE play Kuwait and South Korea take on Indonesia on Saturday in Group A matches .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "22",
            "sentence": "All four teams are level with one point each from one game .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: All four teams are level with one point each from one game .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "24",
            "sentence": "RUGBY UNION - CUTTITTA BACK FOR ITALY AFTER A YEAR .",
            "label": {
                "RUGBY UNION": "ORG",
                "CUTTITTA": "PER",
                "ITALY": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: RUGBY UNION - CUTTITTA BACK FOR ITALY AFTER A YEAR .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "25",
            "sentence": "ROME 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "ROME": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: ROME 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "26",
            "sentence": "Italy recalled Marcello Cuttitta",
            "label": {
                "Italy": "LOC",
                "Marcello Cuttitta": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Italy recalled Marcello Cuttitta\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "31",
            "sentence": "Coste said he had approached the player two months ago about a comeback .",
            "label": {
                "Coste": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Coste said he had approached the player two months ago about a comeback .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "32",
            "sentence": "\" He ended the World Cup on the wrong note , \" Coste said .",
            "label": {
                "World Cup": "MISC",
                "Coste": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: \" He ended the World Cup on the wrong note , \" Coste said .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "33",
            "sentence": "\" I thought it would be useful to have him back and he said he would be available .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: \" I thought it would be useful to have him back and he said he would be available .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "34",
            "sentence": "I think now is the right time for him to return . \"",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: I think now is the right time for him to return . \"\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "37",
            "sentence": "SOCCER - LATE GOALS GIVE JAPAN WIN OVER SYRIA .",
            "label": {
                "JAPAN": "LOC",
                "SYRIA": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: SOCCER - LATE GOALS GIVE JAPAN WIN OVER SYRIA .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "38",
            "sentence": "AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "AL-AIN": "LOC",
                "United Arab Emirates": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "39",
            "sentence": "Two goals in the last six minutes gave holders Japan an uninspiring 2-1 Asian Cup victory over Syria on Friday .",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC",
                "Asian Cup": "MISC",
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Two goals in the last six minutes gave holders Japan an uninspiring 2-1 Asian Cup victory over Syria on Friday .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "41",
            "sentence": "It was the second Syrian defensive blunder in four minutes .",
            "label": {
                "Syrian": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: It was the second Syrian defensive blunder in four minutes .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "43",
            "sentence": "Syria had taken the lead from their first serious attack in the seventh minute .",
            "label": {
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Syria had taken the lead from their first serious attack in the seventh minute .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "47",
            "sentence": "Bitar saved well again from Miura in the 37th minute , parrying away his header from a corner .",
            "label": {
                "Bitar": "PER",
                "Miura": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Bitar saved well again from Miura in the 37th minute , parrying away his header from a corner .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "52",
            "sentence": "FREESTYLE SKIING-WORLD CUP MOGUL RESULTS .",
            "label": {
                "SKIING-WORLD CUP": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: FREESTYLE SKIING-WORLD CUP MOGUL RESULTS .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "53",
            "sentence": "TIGNES , France 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "TIGNES": "LOC",
                "France": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: TIGNES , France 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "54",
            "sentence": "Results of the World Cup",
            "label": {
                "World Cup": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Results of the World Cup\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "55",
            "sentence": "freestyle skiing moguls competition on Friday :",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: freestyle skiing moguls competition on Friday :\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "56",
            "sentence": "Men",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Men\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "57",
            "sentence": "1. Jesper Ronnback ( Sweden ) 25.76 points",
            "label": {
                "Jesper Ronnback": "PER",
                "Sweden": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 1. Jesper Ronnback ( Sweden ) 25.76 points\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "58",
            "sentence": "2. Andrei Ivanov ( Russia ) 24.88",
            "label": {
                "Andrei Ivanov": "PER",
                "Russia": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 2. Andrei Ivanov ( Russia ) 24.88\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "59",
            "sentence": "3. Ryan Johnson ( Canada ) 24.57",
            "label": {
                "Ryan Johnson": "PER",
                "Canada": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 3. Ryan Johnson ( Canada ) 24.57\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "60",
            "sentence": "4. Jean-Luc Brassard ( Canada ) 24.40",
            "label": {
                "Jean-Luc Brassard": "PER",
                "Canada": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 4. Jean-Luc Brassard ( Canada ) 24.40\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "61",
            "sentence": "5. Korneilus Hole ( Norway ) 23.92",
            "label": {
                "Korneilus Hole": "PER",
                "Norway": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 5. Korneilus Hole ( Norway ) 23.92\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "62",
            "sentence": "6. Jeremie Collomb-Patton ( France ) 23.87",
            "label": {
                "Jeremie Collomb-Patton": "PER",
                "France": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 6. Jeremie Collomb-Patton ( France ) 23.87\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "63",
            "sentence": "7. Jim Moran ( U.S. ) 23.25",
            "label": {
                "Jim Moran": "PER",
                "U.S.": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 7. Jim Moran ( U.S. ) 23.25\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "64",
            "sentence": "8. Dominick Gauthier ( Canada ) 22.73",
            "label": {
                "Dominick Gauthier": "PER",
                "Canada": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 8. Dominick Gauthier ( Canada ) 22.73\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "65",
            "sentence": "9. Johann Gregoire ( France ) 22.58",
            "label": {
                "Johann Gregoire": "PER",
                "France": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 9. Johann Gregoire ( France ) 22.58\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "66",
            "sentence": "10. Troy Benson ( U.S. ) 22.56",
            "label": {
                "Troy Benson": "PER",
                "U.S.": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 10. Troy Benson ( U.S. ) 22.56\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "67",
            "sentence": "Women",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Women\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "68",
            "sentence": "1. Tatjana Mittermayer ( Germany ) 24.32",
            "label": {
                "Tatjana Mittermayer": "PER",
                "Germany": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 1. Tatjana Mittermayer ( Germany ) 24.32\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "69",
            "sentence": "2. Candice Gilg ( France ) 24.31",
            "label": {
                "Candice Gilg": "PER",
                "France": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 2. Candice Gilg ( France ) 24.31\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "70",
            "sentence": "3. Minna Karhu ( Finland ) 24.05",
            "label": {
                "Minna Karhu": "PER",
                "Finland": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 3. Minna Karhu ( Finland ) 24.05\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "71",
            "sentence": "4. Tae Satoya ( Japan ) 23.75",
            "label": {
                "Tae Satoya": "PER",
                "Japan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 4. Tae Satoya ( Japan ) 23.75\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "72",
            "sentence": "5. Ann Battellle ( U.S. ) 23.56",
            "label": {
                "Ann Battellle": "PER",
                "U.S.": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 5. Ann Battellle ( U.S. ) 23.56\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "73",
            "sentence": "6. Donna Weinbrecht ( U.S. ) 22.48",
            "label": {
                "Donna Weinbrecht": "PER",
                "U.S.": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 6. Donna Weinbrecht ( U.S. ) 22.48\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "74",
            "sentence": "7. Liz McIntyre ( U.S. ) 22.00",
            "label": {
                "Liz McIntyre": "PER",
                "U.S.": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 7. Liz McIntyre ( U.S. ) 22.00\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "75",
            "sentence": "8. Elena Koroleva ( Russia ) 21.77",
            "label": {
                "Elena Koroleva": "PER",
                "Russia": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 8. Elena Koroleva ( Russia ) 21.77\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "76",
            "sentence": "9. Ljudmila Dymchenko ( Russia ) 21.59",
            "label": {
                "Ljudmila Dymchenko": "PER",
                "Russia": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 9. Ljudmila Dymchenko ( Russia ) 21.59\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "77",
            "sentence": "10. Katleen Allais ( France ) 21.58",
            "label": {
                "Katleen Allais": "PER",
                "France": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: 10. Katleen Allais ( France ) 21.58\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "79",
            "sentence": "SOCCER - ASIAN CUP GROUP C RESULTS .",
            "label": {
                "ASIAN CUP": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: SOCCER - ASIAN CUP GROUP C RESULTS .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "80",
            "sentence": "AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "AL-AIN": "LOC",
                "United Arab Emirates": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: AL-AIN , United Arab Emirates 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "81",
            "sentence": "Results of Asian Cup group C matches played on Friday :",
            "label": {
                "Asian Cup": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Results of Asian Cup group C matches played on Friday :\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "82",
            "sentence": "Japan 2 Syria 1 ( halftime 0-1 )",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC",
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Japan 2 Syria 1 ( halftime 0-1 )\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "83",
            "sentence": "Scorers :",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Scorers :\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "84",
            "sentence": "Japan - Hassan Abbas 84 own goal , Takuya Takagi 88 .",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC",
                "Hassan Abbas": "PER",
                "Takuya Takagi": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Japan - Hassan Abbas 84 own goal , Takuya Takagi 88 .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "85",
            "sentence": "Syria - Nader Jokhadar 7",
            "label": {
                "Syria": "LOC",
                "Nader Jokhadar": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Syria - Nader Jokhadar 7\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "86",
            "sentence": "Attendance : 10,000 .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Attendance : 10,000 .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "87",
            "sentence": "China 0 Uzbekistan 2 ( halftime 0-0 )",
            "label": {
                "China": "LOC",
                "Uzbekistan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: China 0 Uzbekistan 2 ( halftime 0-0 )\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "88",
            "sentence": "Scorers : Shkvyrin Igor 78 , Shatskikh Oleg 90",
            "label": {
                "Shkvyrin Igor": "PER",
                "Shatskikh Oleg": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Scorers : Shkvyrin Igor 78 , Shatskikh Oleg 90\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "89",
            "sentence": "Attendence : 3,000",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Attendence : 3,000\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "90",
            "sentence": "Standings ( tabulate under played , won , drawn , lost , goals",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Standings ( tabulate under played , won , drawn , lost , goals\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "91",
            "sentence": "for , goals against , points ) :",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: for , goals against , points ) :\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "92",
            "sentence": "Uzbekistan 1 1 0 0 2 0 3",
            "label": {
                "Uzbekistan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Uzbekistan 1 1 0 0 2 0 3\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "93",
            "sentence": "Japan 1 1 0 0 2 1 3",
            "label": {
                "Japan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Japan 1 1 0 0 2 1 3\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "94",
            "sentence": "Syria 1 0 0 1 1 2 0",
            "label": {
                "Syria": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: Syria 1 0 0 1 1 2 0\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "95",
            "sentence": "China 1 0 0 1 0 2 0",
            "label": {
                "China": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: China 1 0 0 1 0 2 0\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "97",
            "sentence": "CRICKET - PAKISTAN V NEW ZEALAND ONE-DAY SCOREBOARD .",
            "label": {
                "PAKISTAN": "LOC",
                "NEW ZEALAND": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: CRICKET - PAKISTAN V NEW ZEALAND ONE-DAY SCOREBOARD .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "98",
            "sentence": "[ CORRECTED 14:06 GMT ]",
            "label": {
                "GMT": "MISC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: [ CORRECTED 14:06 GMT ]\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "99",
            "sentence": "SIALKOT , Pakistan 1996-12-06",
            "label": {
                "SIALKOT": "LOC",
                "Pakistan": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC']\nText: SIALKOT , Pakistan 1996-12-06\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_reason": "Question: Tell me the reason why does the entity belong to this type?"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "100",
            "sentence": "Scoreboard in the second",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
