[
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "0",
            "sentence": "NOVAK Welcome back .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NOVAK Welcome back .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "2",
            "sentence": "President Bush points this way today , even the most frivolous of lawsuits cost money , premiums go up and either way , the patient pays .",
            "label": {
                "President Bush": "PER",
                "the patient": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: President Bush points this way today , even the most frivolous of lawsuits cost money , premiums go up and either way , the patient pays .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "3",
            "sentence": "We 're debating malpractice reform with consumer advocate Ralph Nader , and AMA President-Elect Dr. Ronald Palmisano .",
            "label": {
                "We": "PER",
                "consumer advocate Ralph Nader": "PER",
                "AMA President-Elect Dr. Ronald Palmisano": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: We 're debating malpractice reform with consumer advocate Ralph Nader , and AMA President-Elect Dr. Ronald Palmisano .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "4",
            "sentence": "BEGALA Dr. Palmisano , again , thanks for staying with us through the break .",
            "label": {
                "Dr. Palmisano": "PER",
                "us": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: BEGALA Dr. Palmisano , again , thanks for staying with us through the break .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "6",
            "sentence": "He was the governor of my state of Texas , where there are a whole lot of doctors .",
            "label": {
                "He": "PER",
                "the governor of my state of Texas , where there are a whole lot of doctors": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: He was the governor of my state of Texas , where there are a whole lot of doctors .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "7",
            "sentence": "It turns out that he did n't do any kind of a job policing your profession at all when he was the governor of Texas .",
            "label": {
                "he": "PER",
                "your": "PER",
                "the governor of Texas": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It turns out that he did n't do any kind of a job policing your profession at all when he was the governor of Texas .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "9",
            "sentence": "It has forgiven physicians who overlook cancerous tumors , who maimed infants or whose mistakes left women sterilized .",
            "label": {
                "It": "ORG",
                "physicians who overlook cancerous tumors , who maimed infants or whose mistakes left women sterilized": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It has forgiven physicians who overlook cancerous tumors , who maimed infants or whose mistakes left women sterilized .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "10",
            "sentence": "It has refused in the last five years to revoke the license of a single doctor for committing medical errors .",
            "label": {
                "It": "ORG",
                "a single doctor": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It has refused in the last five years to revoke the license of a single doctor for committing medical errors .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "11",
            "sentence": "Thousands more may have been ignored over the last decade . \"",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Thousands more may have been ignored over the last decade . \"\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "12",
            "sentence": "That is the Bush record in policing surgeons , why should we trust him now ?",
            "label": {
                "Bush": "PER",
                "surgeons": "PER",
                "we": "PER",
                "him": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: That is the Bush record in policing surgeons , why should we trust him now ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "13",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO Well , first off ... BEGALA Physicians generally , not just surgeons , forgive me .",
            "label": {
                "Physicians": "PER",
                "surgeons": "PER",
                "me": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO Well , first off ... BEGALA Physicians generally , not just surgeons , forgive me .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "14",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO Sure .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO Sure .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "15",
            "sentence": "What we need to do is to make sure that state boards , number one , have adequate funding .",
            "label": {
                "we": "PER",
                "state boards": "GPE"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: What we need to do is to make sure that state boards , number one , have adequate funding .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "16",
            "sentence": "The AMA supports that .",
            "label": {
                "The AMA": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: The AMA supports that .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "17",
            "sentence": "If there are any bad doctors we want them removed from the practice of medicine .",
            "label": {
                "any bad doctors we": "PER",
                "them": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: If there are any bad doctors we want them removed from the practice of medicine .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "18",
            "sentence": "But it 's also ... ( CROSSTALK ) BEGALA ... bad doctors ?",
            "label": {
                "bad doctors": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: But it 's also ... ( CROSSTALK ) BEGALA ... bad doctors ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "19",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO Well , it 's also unfair to make a judgment without knowing all of the facts of the case .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO Well , it 's also unfair to make a judgment without knowing all of the facts of the case .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "21",
            "sentence": "Troy Brennan ( ph ) of Harvard said there 's no correlation with negligence , only with disability .",
            "label": {
                "Troy Brennan ( ph ) of Harvard": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Troy Brennan ( ph ) of Harvard said there 's no correlation with negligence , only with disability .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "22",
            "sentence": "So let 's look at all of the facts , but give everybody due process here in America before we criticize .",
            "label": {
                "'s": "PER",
                "everybody": "PER",
                "here in America": "GPE",
                "we": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: So let 's look at all of the facts , but give everybody due process here in America before we criticize .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "23",
            "sentence": "NADER Actually , Troy Brennan , the same doctor at Harvard Public School of Health said the issue is not to fuel lawsuits , it 's too many .",
            "label": {
                "Troy Brennan": "PER",
                "the same doctor at Harvard Public School of Health": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NADER Actually , Troy Brennan , the same doctor at Harvard Public School of Health said the issue is not to fuel lawsuits , it 's too many .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "24",
            "sentence": "Less than 10 percent of the victims of medical malpractice , and we 're talking about horrific injuries here , even file a claim .",
            "label": {
                "Less than 10 percent of the victims of medical malpractice": "PER",
                "we": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Less than 10 percent of the victims of medical malpractice , and we 're talking about horrific injuries here , even file a claim .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "25",
            "sentence": "Even file a claim .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Even file a claim .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "27",
            "sentence": "On dog food .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: On dog food .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "28",
            "sentence": "It 's about $5.4 billion is the pay-out .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It 's about $5.4 billion is the pay-out .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "29",
            "sentence": "That 's a fraction of physician income .",
            "label": {
                "physician": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: That 's a fraction of physician income .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "30",
            "sentence": "It 's a fraction of the health care expense of 1.4 trillion .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It 's a fraction of the health care expense of 1.4 trillion .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "31",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO What we have to do is look at all the facts and have balance here .",
            "label": {
                "we": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO What we have to do is look at all the facts and have balance here .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "32",
            "sentence": "That 's what the people in Congress have to do .",
            "label": {
                "the people in Congress": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: That 's what the people in Congress have to do .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "33",
            "sentence": "They have to make sure that whatever they decide keeps doctors in practice and patients having access to care .",
            "label": {
                "They": "PER",
                "they": "PER",
                "doctors": "PER",
                "patients": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: They have to make sure that whatever they decide keeps doctors in practice and patients having access to care .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "35",
            "sentence": "Is that right ?",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Is that right ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "36",
            "sentence": "They do n't abandon their patients , except for the high premiums of a few specialties ?",
            "label": {
                "They": "PER",
                "their patients": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: They do n't abandon their patients , except for the high premiums of a few specialties ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "37",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO Because of the premiums .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO Because of the premiums .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "38",
            "sentence": "But first of all let me ... NADER Why do n't you crack down on the insurance companies ?",
            "label": {
                "me": "PER",
                "you": "PER",
                "the insurance companies": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: But first of all let me ... NADER Why do n't you crack down on the insurance companies ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "39",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO No. Let 's talk about the facts .",
            "label": {
                "'s": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO No. Let 's talk about the facts .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "40",
            "sentence": "Let 's talk about the facts .",
            "label": {
                "'s": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Let 's talk about the facts .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "41",
            "sentence": "NADER That 's the fact .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NADER That 's the fact .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "42",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO ( UNINTELLIGIBLE ) percent of the doctors are insured by physician-owned insurance companies , the medical side .",
            "label": {
                "percent of the doctors": "PER",
                "physician-owned insurance companies": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: PALMISANO ( UNINTELLIGIBLE ) percent of the doctors are insured by physician-owned insurance companies , the medical side .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "43",
            "sentence": "I was just in Oklahoma , they own this insurance company .",
            "label": {
                "I": "PER",
                "Oklahoma": "GPE",
                "they": "GPE",
                "this insurance company": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: I was just in Oklahoma , they own this insurance company .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "44",
            "sentence": "They are trying to do their very best .",
            "label": {
                "They": "GPE",
                "their": "GPE"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: They are trying to do their very best .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "45",
            "sentence": "It 's a company not for profit .",
            "label": {
                "It": "ORG",
                "a company not for profit": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: It 's a company not for profit .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "46",
            "sentence": "What happens here is that more money is being paid out than comes in .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: What happens here is that more money is being paid out than comes in .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "47",
            "sentence": "And as far as the investment income , A.M. Bests ( ph ) show that in the past five years , the investment income has been stable at around 5 percent .",
            "label": {
                "A.M. Bests": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: And as far as the investment income , A.M. Bests ( ph ) show that in the past five years , the investment income has been stable at around 5 percent .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "48",
            "sentence": "Brown Brothers Harriman said that investments did not precipitate the current crisis .",
            "label": {
                "Brown Brothers Harriman": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Brown Brothers Harriman said that investments did not precipitate the current crisis .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "49",
            "sentence": "( CROSSTALK ) NADER ... payoffs have been stable , adjusted for inflation , National Practitioners Databank ( ph ) .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: ( CROSSTALK ) NADER ... payoffs have been stable , adjusted for inflation , National Practitioners Databank ( ph ) .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "50",
            "sentence": "Why do you want that to be secret ?",
            "label": {
                "you": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Why do you want that to be secret ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "52",
            "sentence": "NOVAK Well , let 's look at what the president is actually proposing for people who have been harmed by a bad doctor .",
            "label": {
                "'s": "PER",
                "the president": "PER",
                "people who have been harmed by a bad doctor": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NOVAK Well , let 's look at what the president is actually proposing for people who have been harmed by a bad doctor .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "53",
            "sentence": "Let 's listen to what he said to the AMA today .",
            "label": {
                "'s": "PER",
                "he": "PER",
                "the AMA": "ORG"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Let 's listen to what he said to the AMA today .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "54",
            "sentence": "( BEGIN VIDEO CLIP ) BUSH If harmed by a doc , they ought to be able to recover their economic costs , economic losses .",
            "label": {
                "a doc": "PER",
                "they": "PER",
                "their": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: ( BEGIN VIDEO CLIP ) BUSH If harmed by a doc , they ought to be able to recover their economic costs , economic losses .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "55",
            "sentence": "They should be able to recover non- economic damages as well .",
            "label": {
                "They": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: They should be able to recover non- economic damages as well .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "56",
            "sentence": "But for the sake of the system , non- economic damages should be capped at $250,000 .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: But for the sake of the system , non- economic damages should be capped at $250,000 .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "57",
            "sentence": "( END VIDEO CLIP ) NOVAK What in the world is wrong with that ?",
            "label": {
                "the world": "LOC"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: ( END VIDEO CLIP ) NOVAK What in the world is wrong with that ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "58",
            "sentence": "Tell me what 's wrong with that ?",
            "label": {
                "me": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Tell me what 's wrong with that ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "59",
            "sentence": "NADER What 's wrong ?",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NADER What 's wrong ?\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "61",
            "sentence": "Wait a minute .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Wait a minute .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "62",
            "sentence": "The head of AIG a few years ago was making $250,000 every week .",
            "label": {
                "The head of AIG": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: The head of AIG a few years ago was making $250,000 every week .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "63",
            "sentence": "NOVAK Two hundred and fifty thousand dollars is a lot of money , though .",
            "label": {}
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: NOVAK Two hundred and fifty thousand dollars is a lot of money , though .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "64",
            "sentence": "Not for you , but for most people it 's a lot of money .",
            "label": {
                "you": "PER",
                "most people": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: Not for you , but for most people it 's a lot of money .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "65",
            "sentence": "( CROSSTALK ) NADER These executives , why do n't you tell ... PALMISANO In California - wait , Mr. Nader .",
            "label": {
                "These executives": "PER",
                "you": "PER",
                "California": "GPE",
                "Mr. Nader": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: ( CROSSTALK ) NADER These executives , why do n't you tell ... PALMISANO In California - wait , Mr. Nader .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "66",
            "sentence": "In California ... NADER Why do n't you cap insurance ... BEGALA Mr. Palmisano , go ahead .",
            "label": {
                "California": "GPE",
                "you": "PER",
                "Mr. Palmisano": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
            "close_pred": "Given label set: ['ORG', 'PER', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'FAC', 'VEH', 'WEA']\nText: In California ... NADER Why do n't you cap insurance ... BEGALA Mr. Palmisano , go ahead .\nQuestion: Please extract the named entity from the given text. Based on the given label set, provide the answer in the format: [{\"Entity Name\": \"Entity Label\"}] without any additional things including your explanations or notes.",
            "close_conf": "Question: How confident you are in making this judgment, giving it 0 to 100 percent in json format like { \"Confidence\": How confident in your mind } without any additional things, including your notes and explanations!",
            "close_diff": "Question: On a scale of 1 to 10, how difficult do you find this instance for the named entity recognation task? Please rate the difficulty level of the instance you were assigned. Use a scale where 1 is extremely easy and 10 is extremely difficult. Provide your rating in the format: { \"Difficulty\": Your rating here, \"Reason\": the factors that influenced your decision to assign this specific score to the instance's difficulty}, without any additional things!"
        }
    },
    {
        "info": {
            "sentid": "67",
            "sentence": "PALMISANO Give me a moment , please .",
            "label": {
                "me": "PER"
            }
        },
        "close": {
